<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io</id>
    <title>Sovereign Yusienia</title>
    <updated>2022-07-15T11:58:53.708Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Sovereign Yusienia official website</subtitle>
    <logo>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2022, Sovereign Yusienia</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yusienia adopted new national anthem "Oh Yusienia, land beloved and graceful", and the old anthem will become official traditional anthem]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/vuFNvcIpP/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/vuFNvcIpP/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-07-07T22:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At the beginning of July, Her Serene Highness the Princess announced Yusienia will have a new national anthem, which takes the tune of the Bashkortostan national anthem, and the lyrics are also taken from the unofficial English lyrics of the Bashkortostan national anthem, with some changes.</p>
<p>The princess said that the reason for changing the official national anthem is that now the most commonly used language in Yusienia is English, and it is inappropriate to continue to use the Chinese national anthem. But the old national anthem still has rich historical significance for Yusienia, so it will become the official traditional national anthem and will be used in some ceremonies.</p>
<h3 id="oh-yusienia-land-beloved-and-graceful">Oh Yusienia, land beloved and graceful</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, Yusienia, land beloved and graceful,<br>
Thou rich cradle of folks bountiful.<br>
From the Ionia ancient and beautiful,<br>
To this land natal and wonderful.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>Oh, Yusienia, thou dawn's shining light,<br>
Thou bring'st us to good will and delight.<br>
Like a fine rainbow thou shinest bright,<br>
May thy destined victory be in sight.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>Oh Yusienia, thou'st traversed arduous paths,<br>
Through defeat we've overcome thy hardships.<br>
Thy destiny awaiteth all of us,<br>
Wave thy banner we proud and glorious.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
<p>My republic, shine like a beautiful star,<br>
Thou rejoicest in happy success.<br>
In this land we shall with honour progress,<br>
We chant thee thine anthem harmonious.</p>
<p>Glory to Yusienian land!<br>
Blessed be this land elegant and divine.<br>
With the world we are together as one,<br>
Blossom ye, Yusienian land!</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My personal life trivia and future goals for Yusienia]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/nSLmUNsPz/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/nSLmUNsPz/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-06-24T13:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Sorry for this chaotic title.<br>
It seems like I've kind of wanted to make this site my personal website lately. That's not bad - it fits a country with a personal dictatorship. I'm going to write something here in the first person.<br>
I thought a lot about my name, and I settled on one: Aurora Twinkle. It's a feminine name that can be written entirely in the pure Latin alphabet without diacritics, and is also easy to pronounce and easy to remember. I might try this name for a while and then make it my official name.<br>
The domain of this site will change, that's for sure. I will rename the organization on github to Yusienia, so the domain will become yusienia.github.io.<br>
You probably already know that I have elected the Prime Minister of the Republic of Caelesta. Thank you to the citizens of Caelesta who supported me in the election. I will come up with some of my own guidelines, plans, policies. I'm still the only one in the Democratic Conservative Party, but the other parties seem to be too.. Some are not active anymore, like the left-wing UWU. At least the DCP has gone from opposition to ruling party.<br>
There's not much that can be done in Caelesta's parliament -- I mean, I don't dare to presume my usual petty bills when the president hasn't proposed anything. Aside from politics, I'm still writing poetry and drawing, drawing microball comics or something, although my creations are sparse.<br>
June is the fastest month in my opinion. I didn't go to other European countries, I don't have enough money to go to the micro euro summit, which will be held in Prague. And the another reason is that no one is going with me, a lonely princess without maids and knights around her sounds bad, doesn't it? I also didn't go to the International Congress of Vexillology, although I thought I could. I also think that I need to prepare more for such an event. Maybe in a few years I will be at Microcon.<br>
I'll do a better statistic on Yusienia's population. Then I'll reorganize our partnership. None of this is complicated work. I have some complicated plans, these are holding cultural weeks, making new flags and orders, etc. I'll probably be able to get my hands on those beautiful beads soon. that's all.</p>
<p>Princess Aurora Twinkle (yeah I started my new name here.)</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Princess abolished the Constitution]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/cziElT7iT/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/cziElT7iT/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-05-01T05:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On 29 April, the princess officially announced the abrogation of the constitution, which made Yusienia an autocratic republic. The princess now have all the political powers, and she said that anyone who resisted would be deported or suppressed by force.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long live the Princess! First Constitutional Amendment passed by unanimous vote]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/AAA-ljHdM/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/AAA-ljHdM/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-03-09T21:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<meta charset="UTF-8">
<META NAME="Title" CONTENT="Long live the Princess! First Constitutional Amendment passed by unanimous vote">
<META NAME="Author" CONTENT="Government of Yusienia">
<META NAME="Subject" CONTENT="Long live the Princess! First Constitutional Amendment passed by unanimous vote">
<META NAME="Description" CONTENT="On 11 March, Nea Emesa time, the first constitutional amendment was passed by an unanimous 5 votes in the Signoria, President Tuyết, now a princess, announced the actual entry into force of the constitutional amendment.">
<META NAME="Publisher" CONTENT="Government of Yusienia">
<p>On 11 March, Nea Emesa time, the first constitutional amendment was passed by an unanimous 5 votes in the Signoria, President Tuyết, now a princess, announced the actual entry into force of the constitutional amendment.</p>
<p>The most notable change in this constitutional amendment is the title of head of state changed to Prince/Princess. &quot;This does not mean that our country has become a principality,&quot; said Her Serene Highness Princess Tuyết. &quot;We are still a republic. This is not surprising, since historically the head of state of the Novgorod Republic used such a title. &quot;</p>
<p>In addition to this, the amendment also made a number of important changes to the national symbol. The amendment confirmed the new national name as Yusienia, revised the first line of the national anthem, and introduced a new national emblem featuring an Asian elephant. Tuyết explained: &quot;Elephants are a symbol of strength in Vietnamese culture. I hope Yusienia can become a strong micronation after changing its name. The sea behind this elephant shows our culture's connection to the sea.&quot; The amendment also changed the lyrics of the first line of the national anthem.</p>
<p>All senior government officials are in favor of the amendment. &quot;Conflicts within the government are disappearing, and a new national identity will lead Yusienia to a better future,&quot; Tuyết said.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexasophy: Six Principles of Yusienia]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/1jlYx4qB7/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/1jlYx4qB7/">
        </link>
        <updated>2022-01-27T12:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><strong>United</strong> in one nation.</li>
<li><strong>Liberty</strong> of person, sovereignty independence, and freedom from societal constructs.</li>
<li>Respect for <strong>diversity</strong> in all aspects.</li>
<li><strong>Kindness</strong> to others and self.</li>
<li>Placing emphasis on <strong>inclusiveness</strong> for all citizens.</li>
<li><strong>Neutrality</strong> and non-intervention in international conflicts.</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Tuyết's New Year speech]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/41CqdxQgZ/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/41CqdxQgZ/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-12-30T22:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post-images/1641052976355.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2AUUv0AkdwQ">MSRA President Tuyết's 2022 New Year's speech - Youtube</a></p>
<hr>
<p>My fellow citizens!<br>
We are proud to usher in a new and hopeful 2022.<br>
The past 2021 is the first year since the establishment of the Republic of Amazonia. The Republic of Amazonia has achieved quite a few incredible achievements. We have launched a more beautiful national flag and national emblem, and we have signed the Republic of Amazonia Declaration of Independence, declaring to the world that we are an independent and sovereign state. The Republic of Amazonia has conquered a new territory in Attica, which has a long history, picturesque, and rich products, the Nea Emesa Metropolis, this lead us also join the big family of terran micronations. These achievements have made the Republic of Amazonia shine in the micronational world, and let the kindness, tolerance, and hospitality of the Amazonian people be widely known.<br>
Although in 2021, the COVID-19 is still raging around the world, and the pandemic has caused various inconveniences to the lives of compatriots and me, but the Republic of Amazonia has never been defeated by these difficulties. We are still in brilliant achievements have been made this year. I would like to thank my compatriots who have faced difficulties side by side, helped each other, and built the country together, and I would like to extend my sincere tribute to and all medical workers of Amazonia and all over the world who have tried their best to fight against the pandemic.<br>
This year, the new constitution of the Republic of Amazonia will be implemented to ensure that we have always protected basic human rights, empowered the people to participate in and discussed politics, and established more efficient government agencies, the Secretariate and the Censorate. The Republic of Amazonia will develop friendly and cooperative relations with all allies and make active efforts to achieve lasting world peace.<br>
In the new year, I hope that we will work together and walk hand in hand, with the desire and determination to build an increasingly strong and prosperous micronation, with our unity, innovation, and enterprising will and ability, we will advance courageously in the renovations.<br>
I wish the people of Amazonia all over the country can realize their wishes, and I wish every Amazonian person be healthy and happy, and be in a beautiful mood every day of the coming year!<br>
Happy New Year! Auld Lang Syne!</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 commemorative NFTs issued for Amazonia's first anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/-GR2Dt5Ga/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/-GR2Dt5Ga/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-12-28T17:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Happy 1st independence day!<br>
The Most Serene Republic of Amazonia was formed on 28 December 2020, It's been a whole year till now. The President Her Serene Highness Vân Tinh Nghiên Tuyết issued <a href="https://testnets.opensea.io/collection/msra-1st-anniversary">3 commemorative NFTs</a> on Rinkeby test network, to mark this wonderful event.<br>
The President said that this is the first time that MSRA has released NFTs. Although it is not large in scale, it is a good start. In the future, the MSRA government will make more NFTs for everyone to collect.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSRA occupied the Nea Emesa Prefecture]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/wDCM9rRFe/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/wDCM9rRFe/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-12-04T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post-images/1638724568305.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
MSRA conquered a territory by night assault in Chalandri tonight, the occupied territory named Nea Emesa, this name is from the ancient Greek city Emesa (nowaday known as Homs in Syria).<br>
President Vân Tinh Nghiên Tuyết led this assault, since there were no Imvrassia soldiers guarding there, Amazonia occupied the territory very easily. after the assault, she annunced the formation of the Nea Emesa Prefecture.<br>
Tuyết designed and posted the flag and coat of arms of Nea Emesa prefecture in the official discord server of Amazonia.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The President created Amazonian Academy and awarded 6 honorary members]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/2E6YF5tuK/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/2E6YF5tuK/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-11-26T20:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On the morning of 27 November, the President Vân Tinh Nghiên Tuyết signed an executive order, formed a national academy that similar to Académie française, the Amazonian Academy.<br>
In the executive order, the president also awarded 6 people Fellowship of the Amazonian Academy, all members of the Amazonian Academy can use the post-nominal letters FAA (Fellow of the Amazonian Academy).</p>
<p>Here is the text of the executive order:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Executive order 2021.a8<br>
To support research in the humanities and natural sciences, the Amazonian Academy is now established.<br>
Fellowships will be awarded by the President by executive order.<br>
And now, I hereby award Fellowship of the Amazonian Academy (FAA) to these respectable people for their profound knowledge and noble character:<br>
<strong>HIM Jonathan I, Emperor of Austenasia<br>
Su Yi-an, Leader of Eastasia<br>
Connie Sarah, Leader of Caelesta<br>
HSH Vân Tinh Nghiên Tuyết, President of Amazonia<br>
Hilja-Sinikka Iltanen<br>
Triệu giản nghi</strong></p>
<p>Vân Tinh Nghiên Tuyết<br>
27/11/2021</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazonia signed the Wrythe Convention]]></title>
        <id>https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/9V_tepxFr/</id>
        <link href="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post/9V_tepxFr/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-10-27T18:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On 27 October 2021, the President signed the Wrythe Convention in Athens, Greece on behalf of the Amazonian government. it's an important intermicronational convention, concluded and opened for signature on 15 September 2018. it condemns sockpuppeting, identity theft, and false claims within micronationalism.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post-images/1635433299015.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post-images/1635433309200.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://amazonia-gov.github.io/post-images/1635433315555.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>